Guide to the Frank Moore Papers, 1971-2003 MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Materials: Series X.E: Books, 152176
  - Venini, 1989; 152177 (Box 56, Folder 1)